today i start this challenge
I'm going to try to turn this real one into a business.
in thirty days
but that's all I have
I don't take can
I'm helping to clean up the beach
I'm helping to clean the beach,
there's some can
empty there
I'm just helping to clean up the beach
have some empty cow
good weekend to you
enjoy bye
bye
can to set up a business
can separate a little thing for me not
thanks huh bro
good thing
dog poop
exchanging ideas with the mines of the kiosks
doing so
who can
separate some tin for me man
I can catch
thank you saw
valeu
it's good it's good
thank you brother
where you change the can,
then it's on
walk
fuck not even close to us right bro
You
this was day one i'm going to do with this money
to find out tomorrow
valeu